容器对我很刺激
Containers are really exciting to me.
我开始为 Azure，云提供商工作，作为工作的一部分，
I started working for Azure, the cloud
provider, and so as part of that job,
我每天都在容器里工作
I work a lot on the day-to-day
with containers.
为了我的工作我必须深入了解容器的工作方式
And so for my job, I had to really dive
in and figure out how containers work,
如何为使用容器的开发者和工程师提供最佳服务。
how to best serve developers and
engineers using containers.
所以我想和你们分享其中的一些知识。
And so I wanted to share some
of that knowledge with you all.
所以我们先去潜水吧
So let's go ahead and dive in.
我要点击引言
I'm gonna click on the Introduction.
所以只需要做另一件家务
So just another kind
of housekeeping thing,
你会在这里看到的欢迎-引言
you'll see it here it says,
Welcome-Introduction.
您可以在此处看到它对应于 " 欢迎 " 部分和
You can see here that it corresponds
to the Welcome section and
引入部分，冷却。
the introduction part, cool.
所以我在这方面的目标是为了
So my course objective at this end of
this is to kinda demystify containers for
你让你觉得他们更容易接触
you and make you feel like
they're more accessible.
那是我的容器问题的一部分
So that was part of my
problem with containers,
我觉得他们是基础设施方面的东西。
I felt like they were
an infrastructure thing.
我是个前端工程师或者现在就跟 JavaScript 工程师一起去
I'm a front end engineer or let's just go
with JavaScript engineer these days, and
所以我觉得集装箱是办公人员的事不是为了
so I felt containers were something for
the office people and not for
工程师
the engineer.
所以我就从来没有接触过它
And so I just kind of never
approached it cuz I had that kind of
在我脑海里有一个概念
conception in my mind.
所以我的目标是要崩溃
And so my course objective in this is
to kind of breakdown that barrier for
所有容器都可以访问任何正在进行任何排序的任何人
all of you so that containers are
accessible to anyone that's doing any sort
工程的价值。
of engineering work.
我认为这对所有人来说都是有用的
And I think that can be useful to everyone
from the deepest part of operations all
和设计师的方式是吧
the way to designers, right?
我认为这些容器对整个这里的人来说都是有用的。
I think that the containers can be useful
to the entire spectrum of people here.
我要告诉你这是从工程的角度来看的
So I'm gonna tell you that this is gonna
come from an engineering perspective,
因为那是我的背景，是前期工程，最后是 Node.js
because that's my background, is front-end
engineering and then eventually Node.js
后端工程和所有东西之间的一切
back-end engineering and
kind of everything in between.
但我认为这对大家都是有用的。
But I think this can be
useful to everybody.
如果你之前有过我的课程
And if you've followed
any of my courses before,
你知道我喜欢破门的方法
you know the way that I
like to break things down.
所以我喜欢直接下地去做什么工作
So I like to break go down directly
into what makes something work, and
然后就从那里建立起来了
then kind of build up from there.
向您展示所有工具，以及它们所解决的问题。
And show you all the tools, and
what problems they solve are.
这正是我们要做的
So that's exactly what we're gonna do,
我们要先手工建造容器
we're gonna build
containers by hand first.
那你是谁 它针对的是一个开发者人口。
So who are you?
It's aimed at a developer demographic.
这再次，不是说它不能被别人使用。
That is again, not to say that
it can't be used by anyone else.
这个过程就像是有点 Linux 知识，对吧 ?
This course does assume like a little
bit of Linux knowledge, right?
因此我假定您知道如何更改目录和
So I assume that you know
how to change directory and
与命令链接的基本 Linux 交互类型。
the very kind of basic Linux sort
of interactions to command link.
所以如果这是你第一次跟指挥部互动的话
So if this is your first
interaction with the command line,
你可能还能继续追踪但你可能无法得到这么多的信息
you'll probably still be able to follow
along but you may not get this much out of
你也会在学习指挥的过程中学习
it 'cuz you'll be learning
command line as you go as well.
我建议把吉姆 - 扬的课带给满满的大师
I would suggest taking Jim Young's class
for the masters with the full stack
他们刚放弃了它的 V2 太棒了
engineering which they just dropped
V2 of that, which is great.
吉姆是我的同事
Jim is my co-worker from Netflix.
所以我爱他
So I love him.
他深入地处理了各种交互的 bash 类型，
He goes over in depth with bash
types of interactions, and so
这对你来说是很有用的
that'll be very helpful
if that's new to you.
还有别的吗
What else?
你可以看到我有我的麦克，我会在麦克上做这个。
So you can see here I have my Mac,
I'll be doing this on the Mac.
我在 Windows 上测试了所有东西，实际上我在这里有一台 Windows 笔记本电脑。
I've tested everything on Windows, and
I actually have a Windows laptop here.
所以如果有人看这个现场有任何关于 Windows 的问题，
So if anyone watching this live has
any questions about Windows stuff,
请你随意问
please feel free to ask.
然后，我们可以切换到 Windows 模式，然后一起解决这个问题。
And we can switch over to Windows mode and
figure this out together.
如果你在麦克或者在 Linux上
If you're on Mac or if you're on Linux,
一切都应该准备好了
everything should just
be fine ready to go.
您只需安装 Docker。
All you need to do is install Docker.
如果您在 Windows 10 上，那么可能需要执行一些额外的步骤。
If you're on Windows 10, there's a couple
extra steps that you might need to go to.
如果您有 Windows Professional ，并且它的关键是它的 Professional，而不是 Home。
If you have Windows Professional, and
it's key that it's Professional, not Home.
专业的我建议你安装 WSL 2
Professional, I'll suggest
that you install WSL 2.
但你可以在这里看到我有一个链接可以做到这一点。
But you can see here I
have a link to do that.
这代表了 Linux 的 Windows 子系统，它是它的第二个版本。
That stands for Windows subsystem for
Linux and it's the second version of it.
它允许您在 Windows中直接运行 Linux 。
It allows you to run like Linux
directly inside of Windows.
有我最喜欢的 Windows 功能是很酷的。
It's really cool to have my
favorite features of Windows.
然后，会有一个 Docker 的预览发行版，
And then there is a preview
release of Docker that will
从 Docker 或 WSL 连接到 WSL 。
connect you into WSL from Docker or
from WSL.
如果您没有 Windows Professional ，或者您也不想设置 USL ，
If you do not have Windows Professional or
you don't wanna set up the USL too,
如果我们诚实的话就有点烦人了
cuz it's kinda annoying to
set up if we're being honest,
那么您需要下载 VirtualBox。
then you need to download VirtualBox.
还有 VirtualBox ，而不是 Ubuntu VM。
And VirtualBox and instead of a Ubuntu VM.
我在这里设置了指示，所以如果你点击这个，
And I have set up instructions here,
so if you click on this,
这就把你带到修理科的自述文件里
this will just take you to
the readme of the class repo, and
你可以在这里看到我对所有人都有一些指示
you can see here I have some
instructions for everyone.
如果您有 Windows Home ，那么您可以在此处关注此博客帖子。
And if you have Windows Home,
then you can follow this blog post here.
这只是一个人写的文章
Which is just a article
that someone wrote.
如果你想超越曲线，你就会有 Docker 在运行，
If you wanna get ahead of the curve and
you have Docker running, just go ahead and
把这些照片都拉上来
pull all of these images.
这就给你省点时间了。。。。。。。。。。。。。。。。。。。。。
This will just save you some time later
when we're getting to this point so
您不必等待这些容器下载。
you don't have to wait for
these containers to download.
你也可以的，也不着急。
You can also do at the time too,
there's no rush to as well.
最后，如果你在 Windows 上，你很清楚 PowerShell ，
Lastly, if you're on Windows and
you know PowerShell very well,
我认为这里的一切都可以像 PowerShell一样完成。
I think everything in here can be
done almost as is from PowerShell.
我不知道 PowerShell ，我知道我在微软工作。
I don't know PowerShell,
I know I work at Microsoft.
但是我不知道 PowerShell
But, yeah, I don't know PowerShell.
但我至少知道 Docker 命令的工作方式是 PowerShell。
But I do know at least the Docker
commands work as is from PowerShell.
因为如果你对我有疑问的话，就会有自己的风险
So that one kind of do at your own risk
because if you have questions about it I
无法回答。
cannot answer them.
好的那是指令
Okay, so that was set up instructions.
所以我们在班里有一堆迷你项目。
So we have a bunch of mini
projects in this class.
所以它是一群非常小的部分。
So it's a bunch of very small sections.
所以，如果你不感兴趣的话，你可以跳过一些事情。
So for the most part you can skip over
something if it's not interesting to you.
然后在这里，如果你点击这里，这会带你去看 GitHub 存储库。
And then here, in this repo, if you click
here, this will take you to a GitHub repo.
这里所有的解决方案都适用于各种不同的问题。
And here all of the solutions to all
of the various different problems.
如果你愿意的话可以自由克隆人
So feel free to clone this if you like.
或者你可以点击这里来参考这个特定的项目，
Or you can just click in here and
reference this particular project,
对你也是一样的
that's kind of up to you as well.
好吧好吧
All right.
对于您的计算机，我建议使用至少 8 GB 的 RAM。
For your computer, I would suggest
having at least 8 gigabytes of RAM.
容器可以吃掉大量的资源，特别是在不小心的情况下。
Containers can eat up a lot of resources,
particularly for not careful about it.
我觉得这可能，这台电脑有 8 GB 所以
I think this would be possible,
this computer here has 8 GB so
我能保证一切都能顺利完成
I can guarantee that everything
works well with 8 gigs.
我想你能得到 4 GB的
And I think you could get by with 4 GB.
祝你好运
Good luck.
最后一件事是如果你还在
[LAUGH] And the last thing is,
if you're on
在带宽有限的情况下，这个过程会使用很多带宽。
something that is bandwidth limited, this
course is gonna use a lot of bandwidth.
我们只会拉和推图像之类的东西
Cuz we're just gonna be pulling and
pushing images and stuff like that.
所以只要知道如果你在带宽有限的情况下
So just be aware that if you have if
you're in a bandwidth limited situation,
那将是一个令人关注的问题
that would be a concern.
好吧怎么说呢
All right, where to file issues?
这是 GitHub上的所有开放式源代码存储库。
This is all an open source repo on GitHub.
所以我就去找一个你可以去的链接
So I will drop to a link right
there that you can go and
文件问题或打开的拉取请求。
file issues or open pull requests.
我非常鼓励它帮助保持这个过程的新鲜和有用
I very much encourage that it helps to
keep the course fresh and useful for
每个人
everybody.
那我是谁
So who am I?
我在巴黎喝了两杯啤酒
That's me in Paris like
two years drinking a beer.
那是一瓶非常大的啤酒非常好
It's a very large beer, was very good.
谢谢 [ LAUGH]。
Thank you [LAUGH].
我叫布莱恩
My name is Brian.
我在 Microsoft Visual Studio Code上工作
I do work at Microsoft Visual Studio Code,
而且我在 Azure上管理 JavaScript
as well as I manage
JavaScript across Azure.
所以我现在是一个节目经理，就是我读了很多邮件，
So I'm now a program manager, which is
just means that I read a lot of emails and
参加很多会议
attend a lot of meetings.
但在我职业生涯中的大部分时间里，我都是高级的 JavaScript 人员，是 Node . JS 工程师。
But for most of my career, I've been a
senior JavaScript staff, Node.JS engineer.
我在 LinkedIn， Netflix， Reddit 和其他几个地方做过。
I've done that at LinkedIn, Netflix,
Reddit, and a couple other places as well.
我也是 " 诗人 " 的董事会成员
I'm also on the board for Vets Who Code.
我不是兽医但我很欣赏他们的工作
I'm not a vet, but I quite appreciate
the stuff that they do, so
我真的很喜欢那个慈善机构
I really like that charity.
所以我鼓励你也看看这个。
So I encourage you to take
a look at that as well.
在 Twitter， GitHub 或 LinkedIn上与我保持联络。
And feel free to catch up with me
on Twitter, GitHub or LinkedIn.
如果你把我加到除了那些社交网络之外的任何一个社交网络
If you add me on any one of those
social networks I was except those.
这个课程是由 Fronted Masters 创建和资助的。
And this course was created and
funded by Fronted Masters.
我无限感激他们给我时间和时间
I am infinitely grateful for
them they give me time and
我们爱 Fronend Masters
incentive and we love Frontend Masters.
他们让我打开资料给大家分享这些资料
And they let me open source the materials
as well to share that to everyone, so
每个人都能接受这些课程
that everyone can take these courses.
然后我就来拍这些视频很好
And then yeah, I get to come film
these videos and it's nice even,
在明尼阿波利斯外面很冷的时候
when it's really cold
outside here in Minneapolis.
好吧好的
[LAUGH] All right.
就像往常一样
And as always,
当人们在 GitHub 上启动存储库时，它是非常好的，它能滋补我的虚荣。
it's very nice when people start the repo
on GitHub cuz it feeds my vanity.
大部分都是这样
That's mostly all that is.
不它帮助了类似爬虫的表面
No, it helps kind of
like surface the repo so
其他人也能找到并使用雷波
that other people can find it and
use the repo as well